Every night. I cry myself to sleep because capcom hasn't announced the resident evil to remain now
We have recent evil revelations - I mean it has claire, and it is a horror game, but no tofa mode
So I'm not really happy
The game starts with a commercial than they're at his [parents] dinner party [Claire's] there and Barry Soetoro, Moira
They do something, but I couldn't really pay [attention] because you know what that's a really nice place take out there
But it's just a really cozy dinner party are those mahogany walls how lovely [who] shrimp and champagne?
These guys sure spared no expenses so guys we can't show up and start shooting
[completely] ruins this nice dinner party that I assume some small catering firm worked days on oh
Yeah, they drugged [Erin] Moira. She wakes up, so she's in this dark place
She's in the prison cell she walks out the prison cell you hear russian
And then you're like, I fucking knew it then you see Moira. She's like. Oh my God help me
I'm stuck in here. Please please so you can assume that oh, I'm going to travel around these days
I'm going to be looking for a [k] then I'm going to find it and I'm going to free here
Then the prison cell used to opens its the biggest plot twist in the resident Evil universe
So why are they here?
does it have something to do with the corporation they were working with and these guys that [Sewn] through the window [I]
Highly doubt it so this russian place is filled with monsters and here
We can see the massive generation gap between Moira and claire more. I saw like oh, this is so spooky
I'm so scared right now. This is super scary, but Claire's reaction is more
Russian zombies now
God fucking damn it every fucking day for 13 fucking years, holy shit. What the fuck?
Hater would you like to do the bookkeeping day. No, I would like to go out and fight some russian zombies yay
Fuck off, so we can really see this when more [of] the cares that she doesn't want to use a gun
Normal person's reaction would be more like you what?
Not really the time nor place, Moira, not really the time nor place, but Claire's More well Maura
Wouldn't wanna hurt your feelings
Instead she gets a flashlight and this turns out to be very effective [and] that leads me to make a public service announcement
Listen I know that many of the people listening right now are not east European villains, but if you are
Please if you get the sacred base [buy] some good lighting
Otherwise your monsters will not be used light and they will be defeated by a goddamn glow stick
then again, I don't know these monsters might be super friendly and they are just hostile because of the terrible work environment, so
[the] first episode is picked up into two and in the second part you play as barry also Known by known fans as
[guild] Sandwich guy
Which they then decided to remove in the remake even though it was the best part of the game
It's like remaking resident evil 3 and removing Nemesis
[Sober] [meets] this child [and] natalya she is a child in the horror game, so obviously she has pSychic abilities so here
I'd say something positive is like. I really like the feeling you get when you play as these two
It's like capcom has really captured what it's like to not have anything to talk about
This is of course the first episode. I think it sets off the mystery very well for example
When are they where are they water dose with the catering company eventually get pain?
Obviously the biggest mystery in resident Evil is still there, so the plant is
Inside the barrel and it's still in a pot who waters them
Oh yeah, right mode when I heard about raid mode in revelations one
I assumed that we were going to be like 25 jill valentine's and we were going to storm an oversized wesker
That wasn't exactly true sadly, but in this game. No, it's still not true
Maybe in Revelation 3 but I think it's very brave that an action series like resident evil tries out a horror game
Very fascinating, but anyways if you're interested in this game, you should probably check out another review
And that's the Kilian experience. I will probably do episode 2 next time ah
Maybe not maybe in two weeks probably two weeks not yeah, two weeks